Ki a
[Music]
Hello friends welcome to my channel thank
you for watching my channel and Akshay ki pau
like my videos and here also
we are with a top why this is
Vivo we have ICICI Lombard
it gets a lot of ads according to its stock symbol
this stock is at a turning point one day it can
go to stop or don't
if we have to talk about SMS top then right now there are many small
investments which have to be bought around the roadways for some time
currently the stop which
is running at 100 two a so we have a
fall of around 15274 percent in the range it was respiratory stop can be bought in the range
stop loss will be
your stop loss which will be
on the monthly close of the job is
that till any woman does not come below this level
then we will remain at this position
this is a short term investment where
in stocks you
can keep the retention rate of 122 10:30 portion and period  Of
time and then friends, you will have to give time from 3261,
22nd three months should be in the middle, let's
talk percentage, that is, Thais,
after that this target time is
made from 11238, that cigarette can be done,
accordingly we will try to take the target, this is
our view, you
can increase this laptop as per your knowledge, this stock is in a good range,
if it gets around the pause in Stockholm,
now a good space can be made on the side
because it will
come out of the over protective, if it gets in this range, then
this success is just a view of us
and we will also add to it, so this is
not our recommendation, this is just
a suggestion that it is view sharing, you
can think about trading on it according to your wrist enable, it would be
better to buy around the range of 100, that is,
from here also we are
expecting a short sale, we are
not commenting at this time, so shocked  There is a
lot of job market, he is able to know the road,
we can study from here, however,
in case of short term investment, we can
wait a little bit, for short selling
you will have to attend futures and options,
which is the time bound rate,
and due to that time factor, your losses can be
this, in such a situation it will be better to activate go for delivery
basis research approach,
day trading in futures and
options, these are our suggestions, you can do the same according to your
risk appetite and your knowledge,
if you
like this explanation among us today,
then please share and subscribe to this channel, this Shravan,
thank you for
watching this video.
[Music] [
Music]